0910-387-918 soar.lin@gmail.com 24744 新北市蘆洲區復興路111~15號4樓

#### **About**

I'm a computer engineer with ten years of professional experience. I'm specialized in all kinds of internet technology, including front-end and back-end. My major work is on web server build-up and maintain, planning project and schedule control. Recently, I starting to study some front-end technology, like gulp, vue.js, react.js ...etc.

# Experience

SAGACITY TECHNOLOGY CO., LTD., SOFTWARE ARCHITECT – 2013/04 - 2014/07, 2015/07 - NOW Co-work with the team to build product 《QuizFun 考尚樂》. QuizFun 考尚樂 is a simulation test and learning platform with knowledge sharing as the core, formal operation less than a year has exceeded 50,000 members.

- Won the App Store education recommended
- Won the App Store in 2016 outstanding production APP

EATME CATERING CONSULTING CO., LTD., PRODUCT MANAGER - 2014/07 - 2015/06

Lead the team to develop product 《<u>Eatme 食我</u>》. Eatme 食我 is provide more than 2000 restaurant coupons or discounts in Taiwan, has accumulated more than 80,000 times coupon used. Independent development of <u>Eatme official website</u>, including Front-end interface and back-end management functions.

• Won the 2015 gold penguin APP Award - Special Award

COMPAL ELECTRONICS, INC., DESIGN LEADER - 2011/08 - 2013/04

Porting audio function on android. Design IPC (Inter-Process Communication) mechanism for transformer pad project and demo at Computex 2012.

ACADEMIA SINICA, SOFTWARE ENGINEER - 2007/01 - 2011/07

Develop digital archive system and developing Unencoded Chinese Character technology application.

- Text source evolution (文字源演變), electronic stamp (電子圖章), e-card (電子賀卡) technology license to IQChinese Corp.
- Chinese character query (漢字查詢), e-card (電子賀卡) technology authorized to the WingNet Technology Co., Ltd.

### Education

National Chung Cheng University - Master of Computer Science and Information Engineering, September 2004 - JUNE 2006

#### Skills

LAMP, AWS (EC2, ELB, RDS, S3, Lambda, SES, ...), Git, PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, Gulp, Sass, Vue.js, React.js, Elastic Search, Serverless

## Reference

Github: https://github.com/soarlin

Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/soarlin/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/soarlin/</a>

Blog: https://soarlin.github.io/





